Elijah Ager Luckett

101 Johnson Street Brooklyn, New York, 11201 eal510@nyu.edu

Objective

Seeking a coding development position where quick learners and problem-solving skills are needed.

Summarv

Computer science student with three years of coding experience in both NYU and a high-school setting. Skilled in finding problems and developing solutions on a small and large scale. Background in natural sciences, code and making/modeling. Innovator seeks job in exciting new tech company as developer.

Education

New York University (Tandon), Brooklyn, New York

Computer Science

Graduating - May 2022

Have acquired a 3.4 GPA in my year of studies. Honed experience in prototyping and in product making as well as core skills in math and coding. The year of experience in expository writing has allowed me to communicate my skills in tech.

Lick-Wilmerding Highschool, San Francisco, California

Graduated - May 2018

This schools technical classes introduced me to technical classes. My different projects ranging from tables, to software that my school made allowed me to practice core engineering skills of prototyping, creation and presentation.

Experience

By George, Austin, Texas

Back stock employee/Some Sales Help

May 2012 - July 2014

By George is a clothing boutique. In this summer position I spent my time working primarily in back stock. I occasionally helped with sales as well.

Lick Wilmerding High School, San Francisco, California

Chemistry Teaching Assistant

August 2017 - May 2018

I worked with multiple professors to improve their programs. I worked with experiments and with paper grading.

George, Berkeley, California

Back stock employee/Some Sales Help

May 2015 - July 2015

In this summer position I spent my time working in back stock and with sales. George is a pet food and toy store.

Professional Skills References Math Intermediate **Mathew Culmo** Intermediate Python Boss Intermediate Speaking Skills (512) 736-6870 (public/customer) mattculmo@gmail.com Word/Docs Advanced Excel/Spreadsheets Intermediate **Bobby Wise** Languages Boss French Beginner (415) 235-3408 Mandarin Beginner bobby@georgesf.com

Projects Made:

Table, Speaker, Student activity monitoring app, Lamp, Personal Website and many other projects.